https://www.craftmetal.com/privacy/

Effective: January 1, 2006 thru Present
Craft Metal Products, Inc. knows that you are concerned about online security and privacy information. We appreciate your trust that we will act responsibly with any information you share through this site.
This site allows anonymous viewing of all public information on this site. You can view the information on these pages without telling us who you are.
However, there are some pages on this site that request certain personally identifying information from you. These pages include feedback forms, contact forms, catalog request forms and other forms that may appear on this site. We will act reasonably to make certain that we use your personal information only for the purposes spelled out on the submission form. If you fill out one of these forms, any information you provide will be received and stored by Craft Metal Products, Inc.. Craft Metal Products, Inc. may store your information indefinitely, either in separate or aggregate form, for our business records and as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.
We never sell or share your personal information with unaffiliated organizations for commercial purposes unrelated to the business of Craft Metal Products, Inc.. If necessitated by your request (e.g., if you submit a Literature Request Form), we provide the minimum required information (e.g., mailing address) to allow these third-party organizations to provide their services. Information may be stored and/or maintained by these third party organizations so long as the third party organization agrees to maintain the privacy under the same conditions described in this Privacy Policy.
Certain types of non-identifying information are collected automatically from each visitor's session on this site. This type of information includes technical information, such as your IP address and browser type. We also log and track which pages are visited to enable us to measure traffic usage and patterns.
This site uses "cookies" to recognize a visitor's computer on subsequent visits to this site. Cookies are small files created by Web sites that reside on the hard drive of the visitor's computer and that store information about a visitor's use of a particular web site. The help file of an internet browser application (for example, Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator) contains information about rejecting and explicitly managing cookies on a computer.
Exceptions: Craft Metal Products, Inc. may disclose all or any portion of your personal information if it believes there are exceptional reasons to do so. These include, but are not limited to, the following situations: (1) to correct technical problems and malfunctions in how the site operates or processes visitor's information, (2) to protect the security and integrity of the site and its service; (3) to protect Craft Metal Products, Inc.' rights and property and the rights and property of others; (4) to take precautions against liability; (5) to respond to claims that submitted information violates the rights or interests of third parties; (6) to the extent required by law or to respond to judicial process; (7) to the extent permitted under other provisions of law, to provide information to law enforcement agencies or for an investigation on a matter related to public safety, as applicable; or (8) in connection with the purchase or sale of one or more of Craft Metal Products, Inc.' businesses or their business assets.
This site has taken commercially reasonable precautions to protect the data and information under our control from misuse, loss or alteration. Unfortunately, no system can ensure complete security and you should take steps to protect their information and transmissions, such as keeping user logins and passwords secure and making sure to completely log out when finishing a session.
The Craft Metal Products, Inc. site may contain links to other sites that contain information we believe may be of interest to our visitors. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.
We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy and will post any revisions on this site.
Architectural Lighting
PendantShort PendantLarge PendantSatellite PendantCluster PendantPedestal MountWall SconceWall BracketCeiling MountDirectionalExterior Lights
Church Lighting
PendantShort PendantLarge PendantSatellite PendantCluster PendantPedestal MountWall SconceWall BracketCeiling MountDirectionalExterior Lights
Custom LightingLight Fixture FinishesLight Fixture OptionsFixture ConstructionLighting Layout ServiceProject ShowcaseAll ProjectsContact Us
2751 N. Emerson Ave.  Indianapolis, IN 46218 | PH: 317-545-3252 | FAX: 317-545-3288
© 2020  Craft Metal Products Inc.  All Rights Reserved.  Terms and Conditions | Privacy Policy |
